billeo.com 2009-06-21

# Billeo: Password Manager, Form Fill, Bill Pay, Save Web Pages

  |  |  |  |    
---|---|---|---|---  
|  |  |  |   
  |  |  |  |     |   
---|---  
|   |   |   |    
---|---|---|---  
  |  |   |    
|  |  |   
  |   |   |    
  | **Your Privacy is Our Priority** |   | [](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.billeo.com&sealid=101)  
  |   |    
  | At Billeo, Inc. your security and privacy is a top priority and we are committed to protecting your privacy online. This pledge outlines the steps we've taken to ensure that you have a great experience at Billeo.com, and also provides details on how we treat any personal information you may submit to us. |    
  |   |   |    
  | Billeo, Inc. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. Billeo.com adheres to the strict requirements set forth by the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent non profit organization, whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence on the Internet, by promoting use of fair information practices. The privacy statement covers the site www.billeo.com . Because this website wants to demonstrate its commitment to privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed by the compliance by TRUSTe. |   |    
  |   |   |    
  |  If you have questions or concerns about the TRUSTe Privacy Program, please contact us at [support@billeo.com](mailto:support@billeo.com). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at [www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.   
|   |    
  |   |   |    
  | The TRUSTe program covers information that is collected through the Billeo Toolbar and the website. |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | **What information do we collect?** |   |    
  | 

  * We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature. 

  * When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

  * We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes.

  * Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

  * Other information we collect is limited to non-personally identifying information such as how you use our product on the biller Web sites you visit using Billeo toolbar. The information we learn from users helps us continually improve the experience for the entire Billeo user community.

  * Periodically, the Billeo Toolbar contacts our servers to see if you are running the most current version. If necessary, we will automatically provide you with the latest updates to the Billeo Toolbar.

|   |    
  |   |   |    
  | **How do we use your information?** |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | 

  * To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

  * To quickly process your transactions.

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

  * To continually improve the experience for the entire Billeo user community.

  * If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.

|   |    
  | **How do we protect visitor information?** |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above. |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | **Do we use "cookies"?** |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.  |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.  |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.   
|   |    
  |   |   |    
  | **Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?** |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include Billeo, Inc. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | **Idle-Time Protection** |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | The default setting is to automatically sign you into the service anytime you open a browser. You can turn this feature off, and optionally set an inactivity timer to suit your convenience. After the chosen minutes of inactivity on your browser, you will be automatically logged out of Billeo. This helps protect you, if you forget to logout. |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | **How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?** |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "Preferences" section. Please note that due to e-mail production schedules you may receive any e-mails already in production. 

To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "Preferences" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping. 

If your personally identifiable information changes you may correct, update, or delete it by making the change on our member profile page or by e-mailing us at support@billeo.com. 

If you no longer desire our service, you may uninstall the Billeo Toolbar and cancel your account at any time using the Uninstall menu option in the Billeo Toolbar or by using the Add/Remove programs function on your PC. Doing so removes the Billeo Toolbar and all of its associated files except for the Vault files that contain your private information (i.e. your encrypted password, contact and payment information which you stored using the Billeo service). We leave the Vault files on your system after uninstall because this data is yours. So, if you need to access this information again you'll need these files. If you wish to remove these files from your system please follow the steps defined in the FAQ.

|   |    
  |   |   |    
  | **Third party links** |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).  |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | **Changes to our policy** |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage. **This policy was last modified on August 27, 2008.** |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | **Questions and feedback** |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue. |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | **Online Policy Only** |   |    
  |   |   |    
  |  This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our Web site and not to information collected offline. |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | **Terms and Conditions** |   |    
  |   |   |    
  |  Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.  |   |    
  |   |   |    
  | **Your consent** |   |    
  |   |   |    
  |  By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. |   |    
  |   |   |    
   
|    
|  |  |  |   
  |  |  |  |
